Tompkins Cortland Labor Coalition Publications 6185 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Tompkins Cortland Labor Coalition Publications
1986-1996
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
6185 PUBS
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records.
5936292
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, July 10, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 21, 2015
Scope and Contents
This collection contains issues of "The Working Press," the newsletter of the Tompkins Cortland Labor Coalition (later known as "The Labor Coalition") from 1986 to 1996. Also included are two issues of "The Bear Facts," newsletter of U.A.W. Local 2300; one issue is from 1986 and the other is undated.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6185: Tompkins Cortland Labor Coalition Records 6185 P: Tompkins Cortland Labor Coalition Photographs 6185/001: Tompkins County Labor Coalition Health and Safety Topical Files
Work environment -- New York (State) -- Tompkins County; Work environment -- New York (State) -- Cortland county; Industrial hygiene -- New York (State) -- Cortland county; Industrial hygiene -- New York (State) -- Tompkins County; Work environment; Industrial hygiene; Environmental responsibility -- New York (State) -- Tompkins County; Environmental responsibility -- New York (State) -- Cortland county; Industrial safety -- New York (State) -- Tompkins County; Industrial safety -- New York (State) -- Cortland county; Plant shutdowns -- Economic aspects -- New York (State) -- Tompkins County; Plant shutdowns -- Economic aspects -- New York (State) -- Cortland county; Unfair labor practices -- New York (State) -- Tompkins County; Unfair labor practices -- New York (State) -- Cortland county; Working class; Workers' compensation -- New York (State) -- Tompkins County; Workers' compensation -- New York (State) -- Cortland county; Tompkins-Cortland Labor Coalition; Central Labor Council (Ithaca, N.Y.); Midstate Central Labor Council; New York (State) Dept. of Labor -- Archives; New York (State). Public Employment Relations Board
5936292
- The Bear Facts (UAW Local 2300), 1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Bear Facts, 1986; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Author: Local 2300 UAW
    Notes: no.69 (1986:Aug.)
    Format: Publication
    Language: English.
  - Item 2: The Bear Facts, 1986; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: September 2, 1986.
  - Item 3: The Bear Facts, 1986; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: September 2, 1986. Copy 2.
  - Item 4: The Bear Facts, 1986; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: September 2, 1986. Copy 3.
- The Working Press, 1986, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Working Press, 1986; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Author: Tompkins-Cortland Labor Coalition
    Notes: v.1:no.2 (1986:Sep. 1). Copy 2.
  - Item 2: The Working Press, 1986; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.1:no.2 (1986:Sep. 1). Copy 3.
  - Item 3: The Working Press, 1986; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.1:no.3 (1986:Oct.)
  - Item 4: The Working Press, 1986; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.1:no.3 (1986:Oct.). Copy 2.
  - Item 5: The Working Press, 1986; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.1 (1986:May)
  - Item 6: The Working Press, 1986; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.1 (1986:May). Copy 2.
  - Item 7: The Working Press, 1986; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.1 (1986:May). Copy 3.
  - Item 8: The Working Press, 1986; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.1:no.2 (1986:Sep. 1)
- The Working Press, 1987, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Working Press, 1987; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.1 (1987:Jan.)
  - Item 2: The Working Press, 1987; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.1 (1987:Jan.). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: The Working Press, 1987; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.2 (1987:Mar.)
  - Item 4: The Working Press, 1987; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.2 (1987:Mar.). Copy 2.
  - Item 5: The Working Press, 1987; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.3 (1987:May)
  - Item 6: The Working Press, 1987; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.5 (1987:Sep.)
  - Item 7: The Working Press, 1987; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.5 (1987:Sep.). Copy 2.
  - Item 8: The Working Press, 1987; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.5 (1987:Sep.). Copy 3.
  - Item 9: The Working Press, 1987; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.6 (1987:Nov.)
- The Working Press, 1988, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Working Press, 1988; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.3:no.1 (1988:Mar.)
  - Item 2: The Working Press, 1988; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.3:no.1 (1988:Mar.). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: The Working Press, 1988; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.3:no.2 (1988:Apr.)
  - Item 4: The Working Press, 1988; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.3:no.2 (1988:Apr.). Copy 2.
  - Item 5: The Working Press, 1988; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.3:no.2 (1988:Apr.). Copy 3.
  - Item 6: The Working Press, 1988; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.3:no.4 (1988:Nov.)
  - Item 7: The Working Press, 1988; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.3:no.4 (1988:Nov.). Copy 2.
  - Item 8: The Working Press, 1988; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.3:no.4 (1988:Nov.). Copy 3.
  - Item 9: The Working Press, 1988; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.3:no.3 (1988:Sep.)
  - Item 10: The Working Press, 1988; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.3:no.3 (1988:Sep.). Copy 2.
  - Item 11: The Working Press, 1988; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.3:no.3 (1988:Sep.). Copy 3.
- The Working Press, 1989, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Working Press, 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.4:no.1 (1989:Feb.)
  - Item 2: The Working Press, 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.4:no.1 (1989:Feb.). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: The Working Press, 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.4:no.1 (1989:Feb.). Copy 3.
  - Item 4: The Working Press, 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.4:no.2 (1989:Apr.)
  - Item 5: The Working Press, 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.4:no.2 (1989:Apr.). Copy 2.
  - Item 6: The Working Press, 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.4:no.2 (1989:Apr.). Copy 3.
  - Item 7: The Working Press, 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.4:no.3 (1989:June)
  - Item 8: The Working Press, 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.4:no.3 (1989:June). Copy 2.
  - Item 9: The Working Press, 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.4:no.3 (1989:June). Copy 3.
  - Item 10: The Working Press, 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.4:no.4 (1989:Sep.)
  - Item 11: The Working Press, 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.4:no.4 (1989:Sep.). Copy 2.
  - Item 12: The Working Press, 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.4:no.4 (1989:Sep.). Copy 3.
  - Item 13: The Working Press, 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.4:no.5 (1989:Nov.)
  - Item 14: The Working Press, 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.4:no.5 (1989:Nov.). Copy 2.
  - Item 15: The Working Press, 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.4:no.5 (1989:Nov.). Copy 3.
- The Working Press, 1990, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Working Press, 1990; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.5:no.1 (1990:Mar.)
  - Item 2: The Working Press, 1990; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.5:no.1 (1990:Mar.). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: The Working Press, 1990; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.5:no.1 (1990:Mar.). Copy 3.
  - Item 4: The Working Press, 1990; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.5:no.2 (1990:May)
  - Item 5: The Working Press, 1990; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.5:no.2 (1990:May). Copy 2.
  - Item 6: The Working Press, 1990; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.5:no.2 (1990:May). Copy 3.
  - Item 7: The Working Press, 1990; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.5:no.3 (1990:July)
  - Item 8: The Working Press, 1990; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.5:no.3 (1990:July). Copy 2.
  - Item 9: The Working Press, 1990; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.5:no.4 (1990:Sep.)
  - Item 10: The Working Press, 1990; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.5:no.4 (1990:Sep.). Copy 2.
  - Item 11: The Working Press, 1990; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.5:no.5 (1990:Nov.)
  - Item 12: The Working Press, 1990; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.5:no.5 (1990:Nov.). Copy 2.
  - Item 13: The Working Press, 1990; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.5:no.5 (1990:Nov.). Copy 3.
- The Working Press, 1991, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Working Press, 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.6:no.1 (1991:Jan.)
  - Item 2: The Working Press, 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.6:no.1 (1991:Jan.). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: The Working Press, 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.6:no.2 (1991:Mar.)
  - Item 4: The Working Press, 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.6:no.2 (1991:Mar.). Copy 2.
  - Item 5: The Working Press, 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.6:no.2 (1991:Mar.). Copy 3.
  - Item 6: The Working Press, 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.6:no.3 (1991:May)
  - Item 7: The Working Press, 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.6:no.3 (1991:May). Copy 2.
  - Item 8: The Working Press, 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.6:no.3 (1991:May). Copy 3.
  - Item 9: The Working Press, 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.6:no.4 (1991:July)
  - Item 10: The Working Press, 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.6:no.4 (1991:July). Copy 2.
  - Item 11: The Working Press, 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.6:no.5 (1991:Sep.)
  - Item 12: The Working Press, 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.6:no.5 (1991:Sep.). Copy 2.
  - Item 13: The Working Press, 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.6:no.6 (1991:Nov.)
- The Working Press, 1992, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The Working Press, 1992; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.7:no.1 (1992:Feb.)
  - Item 2: The Working Press, 1992; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.7:no.1 (1992:Feb.). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: The Working Press, 1992; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.7:no.2 (1992:Apr.)
  - Item 4: The Working Press, 1992; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.7:no.2 (1992:Apr.). Copy 2.
  - Item 5: The Working Press, 1992; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.7:no.3 (1992:June)
  - Item 6: The Working Press, 1992; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.7:no.3 (1992:June). Copy 2.
  - Item 7: The Working Press, 1992; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.7:no.3 (1992:June). Copy 3.
  - Item 8: The Working Press, 1992; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.7:no.4 (1992:Sep.)
  - Item 9: The Working Press, 1992; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.7:no.4 (1992:Sep.). Copy 2.
  - Item 10: The Working Press, 1992; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.7:no.5 (1992:Nov.)
  - Item 11: The Working Press, 1992; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.7:no.5 (1992:Nov.). Copy 2.
- The Working Press, 1993, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The Working Press, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.8:no.1 (1993:Mar.)
  - Item 2: The Working Press, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.8:no.1 (1993:Mar.). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: The Working Press, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.8:no.2 (1993:May)
  - Item 4: The Working Press, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.8:no.2 (1993:May). Copy 2.
  - Item 5: The Working Press, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.8:no.3 (1993:Sep.)
  - Item 6: The Working Press, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.8:no.3 (1993:Sep.). Copy 2.
  - Item 7: The Working Press, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.8:no.4 (1993:Nov.)
- The Working Place 1994, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The Working Press, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.9:no.1 (1994:Feb.)
  - Item 2: The Working Press, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.9:no.1 (1994:Feb.). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: The Working Press, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.9:no.2 (1994:May)
  - Item 4: The Working Press, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.9:no.2 (1994:May). Copy 2.
  - Item 5: The Working Press, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.9:no.2 (1994:May). Copy 3.
  - Item 6: The Working Press, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.9:no.3 (1994:July)
  - Item 7: The Working Press, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.9:no.3 (1994:July). Copy 2.
  - Item 8: The Working Press, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.9:no.3 (1994:July). Copy 3.
  - Item 9: The Working Press, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.9:no.4 (1994:Aug.)
  - Item 10: The Working Press, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.9:no.4 (1994:Aug.). Copy 2.
  - Item 11: The Working Press, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.9:no.4 (1994:Aug.). Copy 3.
- The Working Place, 1995, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: The Working Press, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.11:no.1 (1995:Jan.)
  - Item 2: The Working Press, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.11:no.1 (1995:Jan.). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: The Working Press, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.11:no.1 (1995:Jan.). Copy 3.
  - Item 4: The Working Press, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.11:no.2 (1995:June)
  - Item 5: The Working Press, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.11:no.2 (1995:June). Copy 2.
  - Item 6: The Working Press, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.11:no.2 (1995:June). Copy 3.
  - Item 7: The Working Press, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.12:no.1 (1996:July)
  - Item 8: The Working Press, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.12:no.1 (1996:July). Copy 2.
  - Item 9: The Working Press, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.12:no.1 (1996:July). Copy 3.
  - Item 10: The Working Press, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.12:no.2 (1996:Sep.)
  - Item 11: The Working Press, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.12:no.2 (1996:Sep.). Copy 2.
  - Item 12: The Working Press, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.12:no.2 (1996:Sep.). Copy 3.
- The Working Place 1996, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)